<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Tale of Two Bokies</string>
    <string name="key_name">name</string>
    <string name="tale_of_two_bokies_title_image">Tale of Two Bokies Title Image</string>
    <string name="start_the_story">START THE STORY</string>
    <string name="enter_your_name">Enter your name</string>

    <string name="page0">Welcome to the story between two young Bokertons. The story begins with Alex in the early fall of 2014. After recently breaking up with his girlfriend, he is attending a high-school soccer game with his friend Ethan. Alex spots a beautiful girl in the stands, but is unsure if he should introduce himself. </string>
    <string name="page0_choice1">Discuss recent break-up and add her on Facebook</string>
    <string name="page0_choice2">Go Home</string>

    <string name="page1">You deftly land your ship near where the distress signal originated. You didn\'t notice anything strange on your fly-by, but there is a cave in front of you. Behind you is an abandoned rover from the early 21st century.</string>
    <string name="page1_choice1">Explore the cave</string>
    <string name="page1_choice2">Explore the rover</string>

    <string name="page2">You continue your course to Earth. Two days later, you receive a transmission from HQ saying that they have detected some sort of anomaly on the surface of Mars near an abandoned rover. They ask you to investigate, but ultimately the decision is yours because your mission has already run much longer than planned and supplies are low.</string>
    <string name="page2_choice1">Head back to Mars to investigate</string>
    <string name="page2_choice2">Continue home to Earth</string>

    <string name="page3">Your EVA suit is equipped with a headlamp, which you use to navigate the cave. After searching for a while your oxygen levels are starting to get pretty low. You know you should go refill your tank, but there\'s a very faint light up ahead.</string>
    <string name="page3_choice1">Refill at ship and explore the rover</string>
    <string name="page3_choice2">Continue towards the faint light</string>

    <string name="page4">The rover is covered in dust and most of the solar panels are broken. But you are quite surprised to see the on-board system booted up and running. In fact, there is a message on the screen: \"%1$s, come to 28.543436, -81.369031.\" Those coordinates aren\'t far, but you don\'t know if your oxygen will last for a trip there and back.</string>
    <string name="page4_choice1">Explore the coordinates</string>
    <string name="page4_choice2">Return to Earth</string>

    <string name="page5">The time is finally here. The wait is over. Together forever! An apartment in ST. LOUIS!</string>

    <string name="page6">You arrive home on Earth. While your mission was a success, you forever wonder what was sending that signal. Perhaps a future mission will be able to investigate…</string>
</resources>
